a report by ICC security shows that the
two significant factors that will weigh
majorly on the equity valuations during
2022 will be the reversal of excessive
liquidity and interest rate cut cycle
this is due to the quantitative tying
program of the US fed where the com
where the bank is initiating increase in
the interest rates it is important
however to know that in 20122 we will
still be in early stages of interestate
normalization and the transition from EX
Ive liquidity to adequate liquidity will
continue to offer relatively low
interest rates with expectation of uh
inflation moderating in
2022 despite these expect moreover if
you look at the central banks like ECB
they remain accommodative in this stand
despite these expectations the average
yield offered by the US 10year Bond and
India 10 10year Bond remains relatively
low at 4% the this indicates ample
liquidity in the system and the
expectations that the inflation spike is
Transit due to this ICC Securities are
constructive on Indian stocks which are
offering 5% forward earnings yield the
company's December Target for nifty50 is
19,500 while its top picks include
companies in digital infa like ntpc and
L&D as well as companies in insurance
and credit growth like SBI HDFC and ICC
Lombard apart from this its topics
include companies with pent up demand
like Tata Motors and green panel
Industries as well as companies in
exports and Staples like Alim Gujarat
Flur and G consumer also investment
cycle is indication revive is an
indication in the Revival in terms of
significant capex growth uh especially
capex announcements by large private
players in capital in intensive sectors
such as energy and metals